[SPEAKER_01] Amayui Moka English 1
[SPEAKER_01] English 2
[SPEAKER_05] English 3
[SPEAKER_01] English 1
[SPEAKER_05] English 2
[SPEAKER_05] English 6
English 7
[SPEAKER_05] English 3
[SPEAKER_00] English 9
[SPEAKER_00] English 10
[SPEAKER_00] English 4
[SPEAKER_02] English 12
[SPEAKER_04] English 13
[SPEAKER_02] English 14
[SPEAKER_02] English 5
[SPEAKER_02] English 16
[SPEAKER_02] English 6
English 18
[SPEAKER_02] English 7
[SPEAKER_02] English 8
[SPEAKER_10] English 21
[SPEAKER_02] English 9
[SPEAKER_04] English 23
[SPEAKER_05] English 24
[SPEAKER_04] English 25
[SPEAKER_05] English 26
[SPEAKER_04] English 27
[SPEAKER_04] English 10
[SPEAKER_11] English 29
[SPEAKER_11] English 30
[SPEAKER_11] English 11
[SPEAKER_11] English 32
[SPEAKER_11] English 33
[SPEAKER_11] English 34
[SPEAKER_04] English 35
[SPEAKER_11] English 36
[SPEAKER_11] English 37
English 38
English 39
English 40
[SPEAKER_01] English 12
[SPEAKER_08] English 42
English 43
[SPEAKER_11] English 44
[SPEAKER_08] English 45
[SPEAKER_08] English 13
[SPEAKER_04] English 47
[SPEAKER_04] English 14
[SPEAKER_04] English 49
[SPEAKER_04] English 50
[SPEAKER_11] English 51
[SPEAKER_11] English 15
[SPEAKER_11] English 53
[SPEAKER_04] English 54
[SPEAKER_04] English 16
[SPEAKER_04] English 56
[SPEAKER_05] English 57
[SPEAKER_04] English 58
[SPEAKER_05] English 59
[SPEAKER_05] English 60
English 61
English 62
[SPEAKER_03] English 17
[SPEAKER_03] English 64
[SPEAKER_03] English 65
English 66
English 67
English 68
English 18
English 19
English 71
English 72
English 73
English 74
English 75
English 76
[SPEAKER_05] English 20
[SPEAKER_05] English 78
[SPEAKER_05] English 79
[SPEAKER_05] English 80
[SPEAKER_02] English 81
English 82
English 83
English 84
[SPEAKER_00] English 85
English 86
[SPEAKER_00] English 87
[SPEAKER_01] English 88
English 89
[SPEAKER_01] English 90
[SPEAKER_01] English 91
[SPEAKER_04] English 92
English 93
English 21
English 22
English 23
[SPEAKER_08] English 24
[SPEAKER_08] English 98
[SPEAKER_04] English 25
[SPEAKER_04] English 26
[SPEAKER_04] English 101
[SPEAKER_10] English 27
[SPEAKER_10] English 103
[SPEAKER_10] English 104
[SPEAKER_10] English 105
[SPEAKER_10] English 106
[SPEAKER_10] English 107
[SPEAKER_10] English 28
[SPEAKER_10] English 29
[SPEAKER_05] English 110
[SPEAKER_02] English 111
[SPEAKER_02] English 112
[SPEAKER_00] English 113
[SPEAKER_00] English 114
[SPEAKER_00] English 115
[SPEAKER_04] English 30
[SPEAKER_04] English 117
[SPEAKER_04] English 118
[SPEAKER_08] English 119
[SPEAKER_08] English 120
English 121
English 31
English 123
English 124
English 125
English 126
English 127
English 128
English 129
English 32
English 33
English 132
English 34
English 134
English 135
English 136
English 137
English 138
English 139
English 35
English 36
English 37
[SPEAKER_04] English 38
[SPEAKER_10] English 39
[SPEAKER_10] English 40
[SPEAKER_11] English 146
English 147
English 148
English 41
English 150
English 151
English 152
English 153
English 154
English 155
English 156
English 157
English 158
English 159
English 160
English 161
English 162
English 163
English 164
English 165
English 166
English 167
English 168
English 169
English 170
English 42
English 172
English 173
English 174
English 175
English 176
English 177
English 178
English 179
English 180
English 43
English 182
English 183
English 184
English 185
English 186
English 187
Thanks for your hard work English 188
English 189
English 190
English 191
English 192
English 193
English 194
English 195
English 196
English 44
English 198
English 199
English 200
English 201
English 202
English 203
[SPEAKER_08] English 204
[SPEAKER_08] English 205
English 206
English 207
English 208
English 209
[SPEAKER_08] English 210
English 211
English 45
English 213
English 46
English 47
English 48
English 217
English 49
English 50
English 51
English 52
English 53
English 54
[SPEAKER_04] English 55
[SPEAKER_08] English 225
[SPEAKER_08] English 226
[SPEAKER_08] English 227
[SPEAKER_04] English 228
[SPEAKER_04] English 229
[SPEAKER_08] English 230
[SPEAKER_04] English 56
[SPEAKER_04] English 57
[SPEAKER_00] English 233
[SPEAKER_00] English 234
[SPEAKER_00] English 235
[SPEAKER_00] English 236
English 237
[SPEAKER_00] English 238
[SPEAKER_04] English 239
English 240
English 241
English 242
English 243
English 244
English 245
English 246
English 247
English 248
English 249
English 250
English 251
English 252
English 253
English 254
English 255
English 256
English 257
English 258
English 259
English 260
English 261
English 262
English 263
[SPEAKER_04] English 264
[SPEAKER_00] English 265
[SPEAKER_00] English 58
[SPEAKER_04] English 267
[SPEAKER_10] English 59
[SPEAKER_10] English 269
[SPEAKER_10] English 60
English 271
[SPEAKER_11] English 272
[SPEAKER_09] English 61
[SPEAKER_09] English 274
[SPEAKER_07] English 275
[SPEAKER_07] English 276
[SPEAKER_07] English 277
[SPEAKER_07] English 278
[SPEAKER_07] English 62
[SPEAKER_07] English 280
[SPEAKER_07] English 63
[SPEAKER_07] English 282
[SPEAKER_07] English 64
[SPEAKER_07] English 65
[SPEAKER_09] English 66
[SPEAKER_05] English 286
[SPEAKER_05] English 287
[SPEAKER_05] English 288
[SPEAKER_05] English 289
[SPEAKER_07] English 290
[SPEAKER_07] English 291
[SPEAKER_07] English 292
[SPEAKER_09] English 293
[SPEAKER_07] English 294
[SPEAKER_07] English 67
[SPEAKER_07] English 296
[SPEAKER_09] Thank you in advance English 297
[SPEAKER_09] English 298
[SPEAKER_09] English 299
[SPEAKER_09] English 68
[SPEAKER_06] English 301
[SPEAKER_06] English 302
[SPEAKER_00] English 303
[SPEAKER_06] English 304
[SPEAKER_06] English 305
[SPEAKER_06] English 69
[SPEAKER_06] English 70
[SPEAKER_06] English 71
[SPEAKER_06] English 72
[SPEAKER_06] English 310
[SPEAKER_06] English 311
[SPEAKER_09] English 312
[SPEAKER_09] English 313